in two specific rare disease indications, and that will be important as well from a long-term
pediatric.
So, even from a strategic exclusivity standpoint, Lectio is included in the ACC and AHA guidelines,
and I think many of you likely saw that the guidelines highlight aggressive lipid management now
even at younger ages for patients. So I think that really points to not just statin use, but
adding statin and PCSK9 use wherever possible. So I think that all points to a positive outlook for
the medicine.
Now moving to the next slide. Semblex was up 79%. I think really outstanding performance for this brand, both in cost and
a very sustainable state of medicine in the way that the LHR allows for a terminal-based setting.
In addition, we had to adapt the approach to the drug that is already being used, and we have seen
that much of the studies, whether it's drugs, whether it's限-post Creed, or whatever, have been
auspices of preventive medication. In contrast, the choice in terms of medication are greater
outstanding performance for this brand, both in the U.S. and ex-U.S. We see in the U.S. very
strong performance in the frontline setting and outside the U.S., both second, third line and
frontline now starting to pick up. Let's take each of those in sequence. So first in the U.S. now
we've reached 31% first line NBRX share. You can see the steady climb upwards in the graph. So very
excited about that. And hopefully soon we'll be consistently the leader in NBRX, NBRX new brand
scripts in the United States. When you look at the, we're also leader across all lines now with
42% shares. I think that also demonstrates the breadth of interest in Semblix. Outside of the
U.S. we grew 68%. That's driven primarily by our third line leadership, 73% share across our key
market.
But we are seeing early line indications now starting, the indications starting to advance. We're
approved in 63 countries. You can see in the chart here that the NBRX share in the first line in
Japan, we've already reached 50%. In Germany, we're seeing early traction as well with 11% NBRX in
the frontline. And of course, for the long-term outlook for the brand, our goal is to make this the
standard of care in the frontline setting across all major geographies. And as you can see in the
data, we're well on our way to deliver that goal.
And moving to slide 11.
Nowmarket Semblix had a broadly stable quarter, and we were impacted by some of the one-time effects
that we had in the prior quarter in 2025.
So when you narrowed those effects, we would estimate that our global sales growth was about 2%.
In the U.S., we were roughly flat to 1% growth.
So I think that indicates that we're stable, and I think set up well now as the new indications come online for
Cosentex, and that's going to be brilliant for this recession.
Yes, for sure, absolutely .
Okay, thanks.
Great.
Thank you, おй skipping over to Scott, we'll unspoken but know Jim that the current we knew it in the last minute-flight and moving to this coming year of lower Spylo, Yeta.
What we pay Oh yeah, next slide 11.
Okay, next slide 11.
very, very important to ultimately achieve our peak sales goal. So when you look at some of the